♪ Oh, the beautiful gals of '44 ♪
♪ Fill my head when I'm off to war ♪
Oh!
All right, Beatrice,
you got a good whiff.
Now step away from
your father's breakfast
before he catches you a-sniffin'
and gives you a spankin'.
Yes, Mother.
Well, the photographer's
here. Where is Crackerjack?
He was aware that we're posing
for a family photo portrait.
I've got to ankle back to Indianapolis.
If the government is rationing
sugar, can't you ration work?
It is summer, after all.
Oh, that would be a dream,
but who else but I will
make sure the numbers add up
and compliment my secretary
on her tight sweaters?
We do appreciate the
sacrifices you make, Joseph.
Then after a long day of killing Nazis
we'll sit in a beer
garden and enjoy a pint.
All right, Crackerjack,
time's a-tickin'.
We need to take this portrait
before you and I both take a powder.
Sally, why don't you get
yourself some freezy pops,
and keep the change.
Aww, I want a freezy pop.
Oh, Beatrice, you know
iced cream is for boys.
You can sprinkle some sugar on a lemon.
That's a good healthy girl snack.
Oh, all right.
Crackerjack, you look so
handsome in your soldier suit,
like a young Clark Gerbil.
Not now, you two.
Oh, we'll be as quick as
a pour of warm molasses.
- ♪ I will always think of you ♪
- ♪ I will always ♪
- ♪ Drink a brew, I'll see your face... ♪
- Come now, be serious.
♪ When each day is through ♪
- ♪ And days go past ♪
- ♪ Oh, so fast ♪
♪ But memories, they last ♪
All right. Believe it or not,
time's arrow neither
stands still nor reverses.
It merely marches forward.
Oh, really? Time's arrow marches?
I didn't know arrows had legs.
"Look at me, I'm a marchin' arrow."
Honey Sugarman, how
did such a sweet face
end up with such a smart mouth?
I don't know, but I've got half a mind
- to kiss you with that smart mouth.
- Well, that half you can keep.
Oh! I almost forgot.
Say, if it isn't my old
baby blanket, Blinky.
I thought you could take it with you.
Mama, I don't need no Blinky
blankie to fight ninny Nazis.
Bea, will you hold on to it for me?
- Me?
- That's right.
I'll fight better if I
know Blinky's safe with you.
Ohh.
All right, folks, this is for posterity,
so don't forget to look far away sad.
Hey, I'm Tamara, that's Tamera.
- Hey.
- I don't need any help, thanks.
- Are you...
- Ryan Gosling? No.
- I get that all the time, it's...
- No, BoJack Horseman.
- No, sorry.
- See? That guy's way too fat to be BoJack.
- I'm not too fat to be BoJack.
- Yeah, BoJack is much fatter, right?
- No, BoJack is not fatter.
- So you're fatter?
- No! We are both equally not fat.
- Right.
You know who looks like BoJack
Horseman? Phil the stock boy.
Yeah, I see it.
Are you kidding me? He
looks nothing like me...
Meester Horseman.
So you were with Sarah
Lynn when she died, right?
- No.
- TMZ said you took her to the hospital.
- And you held her hand.
- Did you cry?
- I'm not...
- Did she totally poop her pants?
I heard people poop
their pants when they die.
- Listen to me...
- God, is that true?
Because I just read Romeo and Juliet
and that totally changes things.
All right! Ow!
No!
Ohhh!
Hey, Not BoJack, did
you hear they're making
a miniseries about Sarah Lynn?
- BoJack is being played by Paul Giamatti.
- What?!
Why would you get Paul
Giamatti to play me...
meaty roles like that one?
Hey, buddy, is any of
that to fix the door?
- What do you care?
- I don't.
And if it were up to me,
that old house would've
been torn down years ago.
It's a blight on the neighborhood.
And that broken door is the cherry
on the top of the shit sandwich.
What kind of a sandwich
has cherries on top?
A shitty one. How about fixing
your door instead of my metaphor?
Ow!
Oh, darling, don't lift that.
You'll rupture your uterus.
I'm sad to leave the summer house.
Well, it'll always be here,
just like polio and blackface.
Hey, we got a saying in Michigan:
"Put your damn door back on
or you're gonna freeze to
death, you stupid horse!"
- Hey, what's your name?
- Eddie.
Eddie, why don't you mind
your goddamn business?
Tell me, Doc, is she gonna be okay?
I know it's here somewhere.
Darling, we've been over this.
He doesn't need his blanket.
- Nothing we could do.
- I need to find it.
- He should've had it.
- She's dead?
He's gone, honey.
Even Blinky couldn't have
stopped that Nazi's bullet.
Oh, Joseph, I failed him.
Oh, Doc, I let her down.
This was bound to happen.
That's just show business.
That's just war, honey.
Here it is, Mother.
I put it in the closet for safekeeping.
- I never should have let him go.
- Honey, no.
If anyone's to blame, it's the
Jews for peeving off Hitler so bad.
♪ Three little orphans ♪
♪ One, two, three ♪
♪ Without a home or a family tree... ♪
♪ We were lost ♪
♪ Now we're found ♪
♪ And we're... ♪ Oh, God!
Come on, let's head home.
It's only ghosts here in the winter.
What? Wait.
Hey, did you fix my door?
That is a dick move, buddy!
What are you... are you insane?
What the...?
Hey! Stop fixing my door, asshole!
Why did you fix this so good?
If you keep breaking
it, I'm gonna break you.
Well, call me a Kit Kat bar
because I'm already broken.
Kit Kats aren't already
broken. That's the whole point.
What the hell?
Do you even know how to... anything?
I plastered this wall, didn't
I? Uh... oh... oh, oh...
I believe something got plastered.
The problem is I can't
get the right supplies
because the girls at the
hardware store are so annoying.
Heh! You're telling me! Tamera
and Tamara are the worst.
Yeah. "Hey, Tamara, how about
you get some manners ta-day?"
Let me get my toolkit.
Yeah, fine, you can help, a little.
If it means so much to
you, I will let you help me.
Oh.
How come you don't go away
for winter like everyone else?
- I don't fly.
- Okay.
- So, like, in an airplane, then?
- I don't fly.
You don't have to fly the plane.
They got this new thing now,
it's called being a passenger.
I have to ask, are you...
- BoJack Horseman? No.
- What? Who's BoJack Horseman?
Who's BoJack Horseman? He's a
very famous TV and film star.
Or he was, yeah,
before he gave it all up
for a life of quiet anonymity.
Where is he? Nobody knows.
Perhaps a small town just like this one.
Perhaps he's even... in this very room.
But he's not, 'cause
I'm not BoJack Horseman.
Okay.
What I was going to ask was if you
were related to Joseph Sugarman,
or if you were just
squattin' in his house?
My grandfather. I used to come here
in the summers when I was a kid.
Hasn't got much use in the last
25 years, except for the termites.
Get on out of here, Bobby
and Susan! I saw you gnawin'!
Yeah, well, there isn't any more of us.
I'm the last of my line.
Once my mother dies
and I die that'll be it,
which is probably for the best.
No more of you?
- That'll be great.
- Oh, thank you.
That was the reaction I was going for.
I guess that's it.
Have a nice life, Hambone.
- Why'd you call me Hambone?
- You told me that's your name:
Hambone Fake-name-ington.
Oh, right, right, right, right, right.
This is the first summer
we'll spend here without him.
Yes, I suppose that's true.
But, as they say, time's
arrow marches forward.
You hear that, honey?
Time's arrow marches.
Ohh...
Well, I'd love to stay,
but I must be going.
As a modern American man
I am woefully unprepared to
manage a woman's emotions.
I was never taught,
and I will not learn.
Take care, you two.
Huh.
Look at this.
Yes, you have a very attractive mother.
What? No. Why would I...? Forget that.
- Look at that weather vane.
- Ah.
The house isn't finished yet.
We can't stop till we
find that weather vane.
Ooh! I know where this is.
Oh. Uh, all right.
Oh, lordy.
A bit more... is that it?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Oh.
- Hey, there it is!
- Oh, hey! You can't be in here!
Why'd you say you can't fly?
Who's that other person
you're clearly in love with?
I never said I can't
fly, I said I don't fly.
If you want help with that weather
vane you'll clam up, Hambone!
Fine. Keep your stupid secret
about your clearly dead wife
and your probably-related dumb
fear of flying. See if I care.
What are those fireworks for, Mother?
Those are because the war is over.
We've dropped bombs on Japan
and now everyone is happy.
- Shouldn't we be celebrating?
- Yes. Yes!
Let's paint the town
scarlet, crimson, and ruby!
Why, I've got half a mind
to paint things redder
than the banks of Normandy!
Ha ha! What? Too soon?
The Crab Brothers who run this
place are total scavengers.
If it can be pinched, they'll pilfer it.
Ooh! It's still there!
I'll make a distraction at the piano,
you climb up, get the weather vane.
Oh, of course, the twelve
hundred... pound horse
will shimmy up a drain pipe to
get it, that makes more sense
than the dragonfly, who has the
word "fly" in the name of what he is.
Okay, all right, so you've gone now.
You walked away, while I make my point.
- Mother, can I get a freezy pop?
- Sure, darling.
- You can have whatever you want.
- Attention, everyone!
I'm gonna play a song
now, so look at me!
Do not look up at the roof of that barn!
Idiot.
♪ I will always think of you ♪
♪ I see your face ♪
♪ When each day's through ♪
♪ And days go past ♪
♪ Oh, so fast ♪
♪ But memories, they last ♪
Huh.
- ♪ Summer, winter, year by year ♪
- ♪ Year by year ♪
♪ I'll hear this song ♪
♪ Inside my ear ♪
- ♪ Try to restart ♪
- ♪ That'd be smart ♪
♪ But thoughts of you ♪
♪ Haunt my heart ♪
- ♪ No, I don't want to be alone now ♪
- ♪ Oooh ♪
- ♪ Just biding my time ♪
♪ I need somebody dearly ♪
♪ And darling, you'd be sublime ♪
♪ Spring and autumn, up and down ♪
♪ Up and down ♪
- ♪ I keep trying to escape this town ♪
- ♪ And I just might ♪
♪ I'll take flight ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow, not tonight ♪
- Mother?
- Oh!
Ahh!
Sal! Oh, Sally!
- Oh! Mrs. Sugarman.
- What happened when he got shot?
Was it quick? Did he suffer?
Hey, Eddie, come on. Eddie, let's go!
- Hey! That's not yours!
- Yeah! We stole that fair and square.
- Mrs. S.
- Please, please tell me.
Please.
Mrs. Sugarman, control yourself.
Aaah!
Hey, gimme that!
- Please!
- Mother?
Why did everybody stop,
huh? What's the gag?
I want to dance. I want to fly!
Listen, you're sloshed
and making a scene.
Do the responsible thing: have one
more drink to steady your nerves
and then drive yourself and
your young daughter home.
Don't make me go back to
that quiet house, please.
- Mother, let's go.
- Eddie, let's go!
- Are you all right?
- It's okay. I'm okay.
My hands are doing the wiggly
doozle in three-four time, but...
Say, I got a swell idea.
Why don't you drive?
But I don't know how.
Why, it's only as easy as finding
a hobo in a barrel of beans.
It'll be grand. Everything
will be just grand.
Whoo!
Get back here!
Aaah!
Jeepers!
Yeah! We're hooligans!
Faster. I want to feel alive again.
I'd do anything to feel alive.
I gotta say, you really knew
how to handle those salad tongs
for someone who appears to
have never eaten a salad.
Yeah? Well, you got a nice set of pipes.
You're like a Josh Groban who
doesn't also think he's funny.
Okay, now, the house is
absolutely, totally finished.
Wow.
I wish I could somehow pay
you back for all your help.
Don't sweat it.
Hey, Eddie.
Whoa,
whoa-whoa-whoa!
- Ow!
- What are you doing?
What the hell'd you do that for?
I don't know, I thought
you would fly to save me
and by making you fly I would,
in a sense, be saving you!
How many times do I have
to tell you? I don't fly!
You're flying right now, asshole!
- Why'd you make me do that?
- You're welcome.
I haven't flown since Lorraine died,
and now you ruined it.
Okay. Obviously, this was not the
preferred outcome for either of us.
You want to fly? All right, let's fly.
- Oh, shit. No, I'm fine, actually.
- You want to go higher?
You want to see how high we can go?
Clearly, this is a sore subject.
I was wrong to bring it up.
Let's go back down.
The night Lorraine died
she wanted to go back,
but I wanted to see
how high we could go.
Whoa! Plane! Look out!
You want to know how Lorraine felt
when she got sucked into that engine?
We're all just tiny bugs, right?
Aaaah!
Oh, God. No, no, come on.
Come on.
Are you insane?!
I don't want to live!
Why did you save me?
What were you thinking,
hoofing around the dance floor
like a motorized freckle?
- Did you snap your cap?
- You mustn't despise me, darling.
- Please.
- That's before mentioning poor Beatrice.
You aiming to get her killed
as well? She's all we got.
Oh, don't be cross with Mother!
I don't know what's wrong with me.
How am I supposed to sell sugar
and keep my secretary's
self-esteem afloat
when you're having
honest-to-goodness fits of hysteria?
- Don't yell, Father.
- I just can't anymore.
I can't stop thinking about him.
I can't be with people
and I can't be alone.
I don't know how to be better, Joseph.
Please fix me. I want to be better.
BoJack? Where are you? Are you okay?
I don't know. I'm so sorry.
It's okay. Talk to me. What's going on?
It's Michigan, and it's beautiful here,
- and everything sucks.
- Michigan?
- BoJack, come home.
- I can't.
I don't belong there,
I don't belong anywhere.
But that's the thing, everybody
belongs in Los Angeles.
- There's, like, no barrier for entry.
- Oh, God, that's true.
They do let in just anybody.
I was at a coffee shop yesterday,
I heard a guy trying to impress someone
by soft-pitching a web
series he crowdfunded.
Let me guess: the web series is about
how funny he and his friends are,
- just, like, hanging out.
- He described it as HBO's Girls
- but, like, from a guy's perspective.
- What?!
And he's just giving this
away for free in a coffee shop?
Somebody get this guy an overall!
Well, the important
thing is that barista's
definitely going to
have sex with him later.
I've missed you, Diane.
I've missed you, too.
Mmm.
- Is Mother okay?
- She is now.
She just let her womanly emotions
get the better of her, that's all.
Nothing a little operation couldn't fix.
Operation?
What's broken in the heart
can never be repaired,
but the brain, well, we have all
sorts of science for the brain.
She's a brand new woman now, and
she'd like to meet you very much.
- Mother?
- Oh, hello.
It's Beatrice.
Yes, that's right. What a pretty girl.
- What did they do to you?
- Oh, hush.
It's okay. I'm better now.
I don't understand.
Love does things to a
person, terrible things.
Beatrice, promise me
you'll never love anyone
- as much as I loved Crackerjack.
- I promise. I won't.
Why, I have half a mind...
Keep going, keep going, keep
going. There we go, big boy.
Hey, what's going on out here?
Probably should have warned you,
when these guys tear the house
down it might make some noise.
Tear the house down?!
Uh, yeah. You think I just want to
mope around in a shrine to the past,
getting off on my own guilt while
the rest of my life passes me by?
Pathetic, much?
But we spent the last eight
months restoring this place.
Yeah, and then you tried to kill me.
That's usually a series
wrap on a friendship.
- What is a series wrap?
- Are you serious?
Oh, my God, what am I doing
in this backwash of a town?
Do you even get Showtime here?
- So what was all this for?
- I don't know.
Guess it was just a big waste of time.
But you can't change the past.
Time's arrow marches on, right?
I don't believe this.
Well, as a great woman once
said, suck a dick, dumbshit.
- Where are you going?
- Home.