Sarah Lynn! Sarah Lynn!
Okay, one more song.
I'm gonna slow things down.
This is "My Heinie Ain't So Tiny."
Sarah Lynn is very tired.
Can you just tell her BoJack's
here? Horseman. I'm an old friend.
Well, I'll tell her, but...
BoJack?
Oh, my God! Bring him in!
- I can't believe you came to my concert.
- It was incredible.
When you sang that one ballad and
shot fireworks out of your boobs,
that was such a moving
tribute to gays in the military.
We are going out.
Before you go, I need
you to sign these posters.
It's for charity. Doctors
Without Posters.
Okay. BoJack, can you
hang out for a minute?
- Yeah. I'm not going anywhere.
- Also, we have those radio records,
and you're doing the print
ads for Sarah Lynn's Stank,
the new fragrance from Kevin Kline.
- You mean Calvin Klein.
- Kevin Kline, BoJack.
He's the only man who
truly understands my fragrance.
I'll come back in 20 for those posters.
Oh, my God. Being famous is the worst.
- Ugh! Yeah, you're telling me.
- No, but, like, really famous.
- Uh...
- How can I explain it to someone like you?
I feel like all my friends only like
me because I'm Sarah
Lynn, you know.
- Nobody cares about Sarah Lipschitz.
- Who's Sarah Lipschitz?
The lawyer who helped me
change my name from
Sarah Helmulfarb.
Oof!
It is so great to see a real friend
who knew me before I got huge
and isn't just trying to
get something out of me.
Right.
I swear you are, like, the
only one I have left.
I am this close to falling
off the deep end.
I know I'm smiling right now, but
the light inside me is dying.
Uh, what?
But here I am blah-blah-blah-ing about
my own boring, sexy,
thrilling life.
What is going on with you?
Well, actually, I'm doing this new show,
The BoJack Horseman Show.
- I don't know if you've seen it or...
- Ugh, I'm so busy with the tour.
Yeah, no, of course, no, but
it's been a lot of fun.
The ratings aren't great, but
we have this upcoming episode,
and we're looking for
a really big guest star.
Oh. You want me to be on your show?
Well, I just thought it would be
really fun for... the both of us.
You know, like the old days.
I have the script with me if
you want to take a look at it.
Um, okay. Why don't you put
it on that pile over there?
And I'll get to it when
I have some free time.
- Over here?
- Yeah.
I'd love to keep hanging out, but
these doctors need their posters,
and I'm already pretty exhausted.
You should probably go.
- Oh, okay.
- It's all very exhausting.
Thanks again for coming.
Like I said, it's always
nice to see a... you.
Yeah.
Adam Levine
has tweeted his sympathies.
"Today we lost an icon. #SheWillBeLoved
#WatchTheVoiceSeason10."
Again, for those just joining us,
actress and pop star
Sarah Lynn is dead at 31.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Day 75 at sea, there's a
darkness brewing on the horizon.
I feel it. What say you, skippy?
I think you got a
touch of the ocean madness, Margo.
And I think you got a real smart mouth.
You want another night in the box?
No, anything but that!
Then quit your yappin'
and fix Mama a Sazerac.
Hey, is that character
actress Margo Martindale?
She's on the FBI's Most Wanted list
and the AV Club's list of 20
actresses that always
make everything better.
- We gotta call this in, right?
- That depends.
Are we professional blimp
pilots, or are we casting directors?
Blimp pilots, sir.
Then we're not being paid to
discover underutilized character actresses.
We're being paid to pilot this blimp.
Hey, Margo, do you see something
out there across the water?
Yeah. What is that?
All clear
from here to Los Angeles.
We've hit a few delays,
but you'll get your
precious cargo by tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
But the big opening of
my restaurant is tonight!
How can I offer the real Italian
cuisine without my real
Italian spaghett'?
Spaghett' is how Italian
people say "spaghetti."
We'll get you your pasta.
Better do what he says. He
might have friends in the Mob.
"Friends in the Mob"? That
is an ugly stereotype.
You heard the man. Set this
boat's controls to "faster."
Aye-aye, Cap'n.
Oh, I see how it is. Wanna
play a game of chicken, huh?
I don't think this
is a good idea, Margo.
Cram it, skip! Those limp
dicks are about to find out
what savvy film and television
viewers have known for years.
Character actress Margo
Martindale ain't afraid of nothin'!
The boats are about to
collide! We have to do something!
You know damn well, when
we took to the sky,
we made a solemn oath never to
meddle in the affairs of land nor sea.
We are sworn but to observe.
This is the blimper's promise.
Oh, no! The boats are
tearing each other apart!
Crates and crates of spaghetti
are pouring out into the ocean!
I'm watching the same boat collision
you are. You don't need to narrate it.
Oh!
No! Skippy! He was too
pure for this world!
Oh, no!
The pasta is cooking!
If only we had some olive
oil to reduce the stickiness.
But olive oil doesn't actually
reduce the stickiness in pasta.
That's only a myth.
No! I've wasted so much of my life
stirring olive oil into pasta!
Disaster al dente off
the coast of San Clemente!
Twelve tons of pasta have
leaked into the ocean,
and the massive carbo load is heading
straight to Pacific Ocean City.
Joining us via Google Hangout
is spaghetti scientist Carla Hall.
- What can you tell us, Carla?
- Well, Tom, as the spaghetti cooks,
it will expand, smothering the town
and tenderly broiling the
sea life who reside there.
Is there any way to prevent
this delicious-sounding
environmental catastrophe?
The only hope for rescue would be
if someone had an enormous
quantity of spaghetti strainers
just sitting around the house,
but that person would also
need access to a fleet of drivers
to transport said spaghetti strainers,
and in order to strain the
spaghetti fast enough,
the drivers would also need to
be incredibly strong swimmers,
like, just as an
example, hot, sexy killer whales.
Is there such a
savior who could possibly fit
that ridiculously
specific set of criteria?
I don't know, Tom, but as they used to
say on my favorite TV
show, let's find out.
A movie, during the day? Dare I?
One for Secretariat, please!
Thank you.
And, now, to turn my phone off.
If anyone needs me in the next two
hours, they'll just have to wait.
This tragedy truly
puts the "no" into noodle,
the "ruh-roh" in rotelli, and
the "oh, man" in manicotti.
Damn it, Randy. Just pick your best one.
- What's going on?
- You didn't hear?
They need spaghetti strainers stat,
or it's "pasta la
vista" for Pacific Ocean City.
Oh, no!
Come on, come on, come
on! Pick up, Mr. Peanutbutter!
- Hello?
- Oh! Mr. Peanutbutter, we need...
You've reached the
voicemail of Mr. Peanutbutter.
No!
I'm not just running
for me. I'm running for America.
Oh-ho-ho!
Cabracadabblers, to Mr.
Peanutbutter's house!
Mr. Peanutbutter's House the show, or
Mr. Peanutbutter's house the house?
The house. Obviously, the house.
Wow, that was a good movie.
Was it Oscar-worthy? Who's to say?
Ninety-eight messages? Better
listen to them all, in order.
Mr. Peanutbutter, call me
back as soon as you get this, okay?
We need your strainers.
This is life and death.
- Oh, my God!
-  Mr. Peanutbutter,
I'm at your house with the entire
Cabracadabra fleet, but we can't get in!
You need to get over here!
It's a spaghetti-strainer-
related emergency.
All right, buddy, just as soon as
I listen to these other 96 messages.
Good afternoon, I'm
calling from Center Theater Group.
You saw a play once eight years ago.
I wonder if I could interest
you in a full season subscription...
Oh, I don't have time for this!
If we don't get some kind of miracle...
Wait! In the distance! Is that...?
No, it can't be!
Spaghetti or not, here I come.
Uh-oh! Uh-oh!
Sabrina, I'm coming down
for my birthday surprise!
Oh, no!
Well, I've heard of pasta
point of no return,
but this is ridiculous!
Why didn't you just tell me
you made too much spaghetti?
I thought if you knew I made a big
mess that you wouldn't love me anymore.
- Aw!
- Sabrina, that's not going to happen.
We're a family now, no matter what,
and I will always be there for you.
Okay.
Now, get in that kitchen and
eat all that spaghetti.
I gotta eat all
that? That's too much, man!
I never understood why
the Horsin' Around house
- had two sets of stairs.
- What?
One in the living room and
one in the kitchen. Why?
Have you ever been in a house like that?
- What are you doing here?
- You didn't answer your phone.
I was worried about you.
The funeral was huge. There
were so many people there.
I kept thinking, "I did this to her,"
and everyone was just standing around
like, "Well, this was bound to happen,"
but... it wasn't bound to happen.
I'm really sorry, BoJack.
I don't know how to be, Diane.
It doesn't get better and
it doesn't get easier.
I can't keep lying to myself, saying
"I'm gonna change." I'm poison.
- BoJack...
- I come from poison.
I have poison inside me, and
I destroy everything I touch.
That's my legacy.
I have nothing to show for
the life that I've lived,
and I have nobody in my life who's
better off for having known me.
- That isn't true.
- Isn't it, though?
When I was a kid, I
used to watch you on TV.
And you know I didn't
have the best family.
Things weren't that great for me.
But, for half an hour every
week, I got to watch this show
about four people who had nobody,
who came together and became a family.
And, for half an hour
every week, I had a home,
and it helped me survive.
BoJack, there are
millions of people who
are better off for
having known you.
Why did you never tell me that?
I guess to preserve some
fiction of journalistic objectivity.
- Like that's a thing.
- I know you don't want to hear this,
but you're too good to be writing
Instagram captions
for celebrities.
- I'm not just...
- I'm sorry, but you are.
- You know you are.
- Okay. Thank you.
And I wish you didn't get so
distant after you moved out.
- I'm sorry.
- You know me better than anybody,
and you can't not be a part of my life.
Tools! This is Brad.
- I want to do Ethan Around.
- Oh, very funny.
Is this Jeff from Hammers and More?
- No, it's me, BoJack Horseman.
- Wait, really?
Yeah. I think now more than ever people
need shows like Horsin' Around.
I... need a show like Horsin' Around.
Okay, but this isn't
like last time, is it?
Where you say you want to do it,
but then, I find out you
don't actually want to do it,
and then, your mean
publicist yells at me?
And, at the airport, on the way
home, I get one of those big pretzels,
but then, I drop the
pretzel on the ground,
and it gets eaten by a ant?
What? No.
You won't regret this, BoJack.
Attention, customers! Please
leave and never come back.
Tools! is closed forever.
I'm going Hollywoo!
Please, please! I'm no hero.
I'm just a guy with
some bowls full of holes.
Thanks again.
It's funny. You help
out at one disaster area,
and, suddenly, everybody loves
you, unless you're Sean Penn.
Great PR for Cabracadabra, too.
Yeah, you can't buy that kind of
press, and you can buy
most kinds of press.
I hope some of that press makes
its way to this reader
because she is not a
fan of Cabracadabra.
- She hates it.
- I don't hate Cabracadabra.
I just think it objectifies women
and contributes to a cheap and
damaging culture of
sexist commodification
that undercuts the exact reason it
was started in the first place.
But, you know, everything does that.
Cosmo does that. Kids' movies,
athletic gear... statues.
Yes, but this objectification of
women ended up saving
lots of lives,
many of whom were also
women, so, therefore, not sexist?
I can't argue with that.
Well, the good news is, you
don't have to anymore,
because I'm selling the company!
Oh!
You know, it's really too
bad you shut down the agency,
because, if you could've held
out for just a couple more months,
right now, Vim would
be rolling in money.
I'm really happy for you,
but I'm actually enjoying my time off.
Ralph and I went on vacation.
Can you believe this
one had never been to Cairo?
Those Egyptians really
know how to treat a cat.
And what do you do, Ralph, that you
can just hop on a plane to Cairo?
Well, I own and operate my
own greeting card company,
but everywhere I go, I have a free room.
- Oh, because you're a mouse?
- What? No.
- Because I'm a Stilton.
- Oh, my God! Like Stilton hotels?
I gotta take this. It's my new agent.
- Hello?
- So, anyway...
Another
offer? That's incredible!
- Ralph and I...
- They want to pay me how much?
That is a lot of zeroes.
Sign me up.
What is he doing? You
never take the first offer.
Hey, Diane,
what have you been up to?
Well, I'm just weighing my options.
I don't want to just
jump into my next...
You know what you should do?
Ralph's sister Stefani is
starting a new website.
It's a feminism/lifestyle/celebrity
blog/ newsletter/community hub,
and she's looking for a partner/editor/
"bomb-ass super bitch," her words.
You'd be perfect for
it. I'll set a meeting.
Yeah, that could be cool. Why
don't you give her my info?
No, no. I'll just set a meeting. It's
easy. I'm not doing anything else.
- Except enjoying your time off, right?
- Right.
Wow, another amazing offer!
It's like everywhere I
look, money, money, money!
Even ten percent of this
would be quite a windfall.
- I like your friends.
- Yeah.
And I like this.
Mwah!
- This is working.
- I like it, too.
That was smart of you to
think of Diane for GirlCrush.
You're always making great connections.
That's probably why you
were such a good manager.
- I wasn't a manager. I was an agent.
- Oh, right. Sorry.
Well, whatever it was,
I'm glad that it's over,
because I don't want to
share you with anybody.
Oh, my God! Maybe that was the problem!
Maybe what was the problem?
All this time, I
thought I was an agent,
but what if what I was
really supposed to be was a manager?
What's the difference?
It's a completely
different line of work.
An agent helps a client find jobs,
but a manager helps
manage a client's career.
- It sounds exactly the same.
- I think I'm having an epiphany.
It's like I've been wearing the
wrong bra size this whole time.
Okay, if this is the
thing that'll make you happy,
then I totally support you,
but it kind of sounds like you're
just going back to
the same sort of job
that made you
miserable for the last 20 years.
No, Ralph. Don't you get
it? This is a new beginning.
- I'm gonna be a manager!
- Oh...
- Wow.
- Takes you back, doesn't it?
Listen, before
everyone gets here tomorrow,
I have a couple notes on the script.
Too many "yowza-yowza
bo-bowzas," or not enough?
No. On page 18,
Ethan and the Horse try to get
Julia to put on the roller skates,
and she runs out of the room crying,
and then, the Horse
says, "That went well."
Anything about that feel weird to you?
No, see, the Horse is being sarcastic.
It didn't go well. So, when the Horse
says, "That went well," it's funny.
- Dramatic irony.
- No, I get the irony.
That's not the issue. This
is a guaranteed laugh.
You're giving me the cut to commercial.
And that's a problem for you?
This is Ethan Around. It's your show,
and we need to tell the audience that.
- You can't give all the best jokes to me.
- I don't know, BoJack.
You really think I'm
ready for a "That went well"?
- You tell me. Let's hear it.
- That went well!
You're pushing too hard. The
line's funny. Trust the line.
That went well.
Great. Now let me
hear you throw it away.
- Oh, like a... That went well.
- Yes, that was great!
And that was a great
look, with the eyebrow.
- What if we both did that?
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm looking at you like,
"This parenting thing is
gonna be harder than I thought,"
and you're looking at me like, "Now
you see what I had to go through."
- Exactly. Let's try it.
- Well, that went well.
Hmm...
- Oh, my God. Chills.
- Yeah, you feel that?
- Yeah.
- Now that's how you cut to commercial.
That actually went well.
This place has really gone
downhill since they got that new chef.
As I was saying, I don't think the
site needs to be just one thing.
I think it can be a big
umbrella, but, like, also not an umbrella.
That's GirlCroosh.
Sorry, did you say "croosh"?
Oh, you do not need to
apologize here, Diane.
"Sorry" is a crutch and
"crutch" is an ableist term.
I'm sorry if that shocks you, but
I will not apologize for it.
So, can I ask what the
business model is here?
Diane, I'm rich. I'm not
doing this to make money.
I'm doing this to make
connections with real women
and extend my personal brand
as a real down-to-earth chica
who cares about real women.
Well, you know what's
great about that is,
if you're not beholden to ad
revenue, your writers can...
Yes! That is exactly the idea,
whatever you were about to say.
I want to give you a
real support system,
because, honestly,
Diane, what you do is so croosh.
That shit you said about Hank
Hippopopalous last year
was supernova red hot badass.
It wasn't even on
fleek. Fleek was on it.
Thank you.
One thing though. Is
anything off limits?
Like, if you had to write a piece about
your husband, could you do it?
- Why would I have to do that?
- I don't know.
Because his company is
basically Hooters on wheels?
- He's actually selling that company.
- Well, he's still a public figure.
What if Mr. Peanutbutter
does something problematic
and you have a real hot take?
If I have a problem
with my husband, I'm
gonna talk to him about it directly.
Okay, so what if you did
that and he didn't listen,
and you knew that, as
much as you love him
and as much as he loves
you, he's never gonna get it?
And meanwhile, you also knew that
all your readers looked up to you
and wanted to read your opinion?
Would you write about it then?
- You got the job?
- I got the job!
Oh, my God! Can you believe it?
In the same week, I sell a
company for millions of dollars
and you get a job writing for a blog.
When it rains, it pours, huh?
And over here is where you
can keep all of your receipts,
in your leaning tower of receipts.
I think my client can
handle it from here.
This meeting is just to give you and
the other former
partners your money.
- Sign here.
- Okay.
And here's your check. That's
all this needed to be.
Whoa!
This is for eight million dollars.
Well, you are a one-third
owner. What did you expect?
Todd, as a millionaire? That'll
lead to some interesting stories.
What an exciting development.
How's that gonna change the dynamic?
- I guess we're gonna find out, right?
- You can leave now.
Hooray! Todd's in the one percent.
Oh, uh...
- Hey.
- Hi.
Julia, this ice cream is only for
girls who try on their roller skates.
- So, what do you say?
- Uh, I'm gonna swipe left on that idea.
Cut! We got a lighting issue.
What? I'll be in my trailer.
- Hey, Chloe, that was really funny.
- Thanks.
- Are you having
fun? - Mm-hmm.
You got any friends in the audience?
No friends, but my
mommy and my daddy.
Oh. You want to know a
secret about your mommy and daddy?
- What?
- They are really proud of you.
Oh, I know that.
What do you want to be
when you grow up, Chloe?
What do you mean? I want to be like you.
- Like me?
- I want to be famous.
Oh, no.
- BoJack?
-  Oh, God.
- Is everything okay?
- I can't be here.
I can't do this again. This isn't right.
- What do you mean?
- I need to go.
We need to shoot the
rest of this episode.
I'm sorry. I just...
I don't belong here.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
So, what are you gonna do with
your eight million dollars?
First, I'm gonna get a really
fancy hat, like, really fancy.
Then, I'm gonna get a T-shirt that
says, "Hey, look at my hat."
What about you?
I've always wanted to go
to a super nice restaurant
and order everything on the menu.
Oh, yeah! That's, like, first
day millionaire stuff.
We should go sometime, together.
- Todd, can I ask you something?
- Of course.
What's your deal?
I feel like you like
me, but you don't like me,
but you like me, and I
don't know what that is.
Are you gay?
Whoa. Why would you even...?
You can tell me if you're gay. It's fine.
This isn't the 1600s, or
some places in the present.
I'm not gay. I mean, I don't think I am,
but... I don't think
I'm straight, either.
I don't know what I am.
I think I might be nothing.
- Oh. Well, that's okay.
- Yeah?
Yeah, of course.
Thank you so much.
Oh, crap! I accidentally tipped the
waitress eight million dollars!
Well, guess I'm broke again.
Who could that be?
Pizza?
Katrina, you're not pizza.
Ugh. This fight again?
Listen, butt-sniffer, I work for
a guy and we're looking for a guy.
You're supposed to be this big hero now,
so someone brought your
name up in a meeting,
and, now, I have an opportunity for you.
Oh, is it being married to you
again? Because I'd
rather get euthanized.
Spoiler alert from Marley & Me.
That wasn't a spoiler until
you said the name of the movie.
If you've got a gig for me, you
can go through my new manager.
Oh, I'm not talking about a gig.
Then what are you talking about?
Oh, my God, this is so classic Katrina!
How would you like to be the governor?
Whoa.
- Of California?
- Yes, of California.
Who's at the door? Is it pizza?
Welcome back. Your
first meeting's at 10:00,
and you have a lunch at 11:30.
- Thank you, Judah.
- Also, I have someone on line two
trying to get in
touch with BoJack Horseman.
I have no idea how she got this
number. It sounds like
it's a teenage girl.
Tell her I don't work for BoJack.
Mm-hmm. I'm sorry. We can't help you.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --