sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
♪ Joy to the world, Todd is here ♪
♪ He drank up all your beer ♪
Oh, I'm sorry, did I startle you
with holiday cheer
and good will towards man?
No, I just had this terrible
dream that you were a person
that existed and that you were
in my room for some reason.
And then I woke up and it was true.
Do you know what day it is?
Oh, shit, is it like our
anniversary of that one
day that I forgot to tell
you how annoying you are?
No, that was July 14th.
You can remember it
because it's also Bastille Day.
- Christ, are you annoying.
- BoJack, it's Christmas!
Well, don't get too excited.
I didn't get you shit.
Ha! Shows what you know.
When you were passed out,
I used your credit card
to buy me this new hat.
Merry Christmas to me.
It looks exactly like your old hat.
Yeah, it's my favorite kind of hat.
Thanks, buddy!
Okay, great, Christmas
transaction complete.
Please leave now.
Or we could watch
Sabrina's Christmas Wish.
Hard pass.
What? Come on,
you love Horsin' Around!
Yeah, but I always skip
the Christmas ones.
Because the themes
of family and togetherness
are a chilling reminder
of your own isolation?
No, but thank you for that.
Todd, special holiday episodes
are always stupid.
Cynical cash grabs by greedy corporations
looking to squeeze
a few extra Nielsen points
out of sentimental claptrap
for mush-brained idiots who'd
rather spend their Christmas
watching a fake family on TV
than actually trying
to have a conversation
with their own dumb families.
I like it when people on TV
hug each other.
Oh, come on, buddy!
It's Christmas!
Fine, if it'll make you shut up,
I begrudgingly acquiesce
to a half-hour of shared
holiday acknowledgment,
but only because I get a residual check
every time somebody watches one of them.
Hurray!
Begrudging acquiescence!
♪ Three little orphans, one, two, three ♪
♪ Without a home or a family tree ♪
♪ Until this horse said, "Live with me!" ♪
♪ And now we've got a new family ♪
♪ We're laughin' and learnin'
and lovin' a lot ♪
♪ Every new day is a dream ♪
♪ We were lost and now we're found ♪
♪ And we're ♪
♪ Horsin' Around ♪
Horsin' Around is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Eggs sunny side up,
just like you like 'em.
The hash has been thoroughly browned
and your pancakes have
extra chocolate chips.
- Any questions?
- Just the one.
Who are you and
what have you done with Olivia?
Can't a sweet, young,
lovable orphan make breakfast
for her favorite horse without
having ulterior motives?
You're right,
I'm sorry, Olivia, this is very sweet.
- And speaking of ulterior motives...
- Well, I walked into that one.
That cute leather jacket I like
is on sale at the galleria.
As always, all roads lead
to a cute leather jacket.
I gotta say, I've never understood
the appeal of fashionable clothing.
Um, that's the understatement
of the century.
Trends come and go,
but give me a pair
of sensible winter socks,
and for years to come,
I can keep my tootsies toasty.
Haven't you kids ever heard
that it's better to give than to receive?
Well, by that logic,
isn't giving you the opportunity
to give me a leather jacket
really the best gift of all?
Well, I've heard of
a one jacket mind,
but this is ridiculous.
"One jacket mind"?
What the hell is a one jacket mind?
I just want to look good
when I'm on the back
of Joey Saratoga's motorcycle.
Besides, I've never had a Christmas before
and I want to make sure
this one's really special.
Hold on, you mean to tell me you've
never had a Christmas at the orphanage?
- What's a Christ... mas?
- What's a Christmas?
Wha... Only the most
wonderful time of the year.
You hang up stockings, sing carols,
- and wait up for Santa Claus.
- What's a Santa Claus?
- Is there an echo in here?
Santa Claus is the best.
He's this jolly old fat man
who lives up at the North Pole,
and every year he flies all over the world
leaving presents for
all the good boys and girls.
We get presents
just for being good?
That's too much, man.
That's my favorite line!
That's right,
but you have to be really good
because Santa Claus is always watching.
Even when we go to the bathroom?
That's too much, man.
Yeah, she said it again!
This Santa Claus guy sounds
like a real piece of work.
Yowza-yowza-bo-bowza!
You kids just wait,
this is gonna be the best
Christmas you ever had.
- So, better than no Christmas?
- A thousand times better.
A thousand times zero is still zero.
- Ethan, you want those winter socks?
- Do I?
Then don't be such
a wise guy over here, eh?
- Is Mr. Liberatore in?
- Look at you all business.
No, "Hello, Tracy.
Your hair looks nice, Tracy.
How's your mother, Tracy?"
Ah, sorry, Trace,
I'm just trying to get ahead
so I don't have to work
on Christmas this year.
Since when do you care
about workin' on Christmas?
Are those little rug
rats making you soft?
No way, I'm still the top
earner at this firm.
I'll buzz Mr. Liberatore
and let him know you're here.
I know he wanted to check your
progress on the Manzanita briefs.
Tracy, if you wanted
to see my briefs,
all you had to do was ask.
Why, if I didn't know any better,
I'd say you were flirting with me.
Kiss her!
Mr. Liberatore is gonna make me
come in on Christmas, I can feel it.
You know, he has got to be the meanest,
snootiest, penny-pinchingest...
And he's right behind me, isn't he?
Actually, I'm
listening over the intercom.
Oh!
I can't say I'm not disappointed.
Time was, I thought you were a go-getter.
Hey, I go, I get.
Ever since those orphans moved in,
you've become awfully distracted.
If you want to be made partner,
you'll have to show some initiative.
You know, Jacob Goldstein's
coming in on Christmas.
- Jacob Goldstein's Jewish!
- He is?
The boys at the country club
are not gonna like that.
Anyway, you can spend Christmas
morning with your little tater tots,
but I want you in here by the afternoon.
Remember, this is your career
we're talking about.
- It's quiet.
- Too quiet.
♪ And a Goober in a pear tree ♪
Go home, Goober!
For your information,
I was invited here personally
by The Horse himself to sprinkle
a little holiday magic
into your dull, Gooberless lives.
Since when does Santa wear sunglasses?
I thought it was time old Saint Nick
got a bit of an update,
you know what I'm sayin'?
Let me guess, instead of "Ho, Ho, Ho,"
it's "Yo, Yo, Yo."
And, uh, maybe later I could get you
under the mistletoe-toe-toe?
I've got three words for you Goober:
No, no, no.
Kiss her!
All right, Sabrina,
are you ready for the big surprise?
A tree inside the house?
Now I've seen everything.
And that's not all.
Look who came to visit.
- Hey!
Go home, Goober.
No, that's not Goober, it's Santa.
Please, I'd recognize
that cologne anywhere.
You had to wear the cologne.
Ha, classic Goober.
Are you gonna keep talking?
'Cause I'll just pause it.
Okay, okay, I won't talk.
- You're getting into it, aren't you?
- No, why are we doing this?
You have to watch cheesy old
holiday specials on Christmas,
- it's tradition.
- Why? They're never any good.
Things don't become traditions
because they're good, BoJack.
They become good
because they're traditions.
You know, you can't just
make yourself sound smart
- by saying things backwards.
- Oh, I can't, can't I?
Still don't believe I let you
talk me into this.
And I still don't believe Goober
ended up molesting all those Laker Girls.
Goober did not molest those Laker Girls,
the actor who played Goober
molested those Laker Girls.
- Hey, this is nice, right?
- No, shut up.
All right, all right,
little lady, you got me.
But, uh, listen,
I'm actually workin' for Santa
as one of his helpers,
so anything you say to me
I can relay to the big man himself.
Is there anything you want
to ask Santa for?
Now's your chance, anything you want.
Well, I guess what I really want
is a personalized pencil set.
A pencil set? Sabrina!
At the orphanage,
I always had to share everything.
If I pencils that had my name on them,
everyone would know,
"Hey, these pencils are Sabrina's!
Hands off, bumsky!"
I don't think you're getting
this whole Christmas thing.
You can ask for anything,
you don't have to be shy.
Well, I guess I wouldn't mind
a Pretty Pony Princess play set.
Now you're thinking Christmas.
Keep going, what do you want
more than anything else in the world?
- I can ask Santa for anything?
- Anything at all.
And if I'm good,
Santa has to give it to me?
That's the deal, as long as you're good,
all your Christmas dreams will come true.
Okay, I know what I want.
Santa, I want my Mommy
and Daddy to come back!
- Aww.
- Ooh!
- This is gonna be the best Christmas ever.
Look how sad you are,
you're a really good actor.
Are you gonna interrupt
every five minutes?
- Because I will ask you to leave.
- And spend Christmas by yourself?
No one should be alone on Christmas.
Did we learn nothing from
John McClane in "Die Hard"?
John McClane was alone on Christmas,
that's how he saved the day.
He wasn't alone,
he had that cop helping him,
the dad from Family Matters.
That wasn't the dad from Family Matters,
it was just the same actor.
I'm pretty sure
it's supposed to be the same character,
- they're both cops.
- Yeah, but one was a cop in Los Angeles
- and the other was a cop in Chicago.
- Maybe he moved.
He didn't move,
they had different names!
Witness Protection.
- Hey, this is nice, right?
- No!
Oh, Charles Krauthammer,
you have done it again.
Yes, Mr. Liberatore.
Of course, Mr. Liberatore,
I'll get right on it, sir.
Yeesh, I've heard of being a work
horse, but this is ridiculous.
I just hate that he's making you
work on Christmas.
- What is this, Communist Russia?
- I know, it's a bummer,
but we can find other times
to be together.
Hey, maybe I'll chaperone your prom.
I can meet all your friends,
talk you up to this Joey Saratoga fella,
maybe even take a spin on the dance floor.
You know, back in my day,
I could really bust the regular move.
Well, just got done shoveling the walk!
I'm being really good just so
there's no confusion for Santa
over whether or not he should
make my Christmas wish come true.
Santa, if you're listening,
I'm Sabrina!
Sabrina, I'm glad you're getting
into the Christmas spirit,
but, you know, bringing your
parents back is a pretty tall order.
Not for Santa.
Santa can do anything,
just as long as I believe, right, guys?
You wanna handle this one?
Sabrina, there are some things
even Santa can't do.
Okay, I get what's happening.
You're trying to make me think
Santa won't bring me my Mommy
and Daddy so that when he does,
I'll be even more surprised.
Just when I thought Christmas
couldn't get any more magical.
See you later!
I've heard of great
Christmas expectations,
but this is ridiculous.
Now no matter what Santa brings,
she'll go from "reindeer" to "reindon't."
What are we gonna do?
Horse, maybe you should tell her
that her parents aren't coming.
I can't do that, she'll never
believe in Santa Claus again.
And we're sure Santa can't
bring people back from the dead?
On Dancer, on Prancer,
on Necromancer?
I'm thinkin' no.
Oh, my God, I got it.
Maybe if we can trick her into being
bad, she'll think Santa's mad at her.
That way, when Christmas comes
and her parents don't show up,
she'll just think it's her own fault.
Brilliant! She'll still believe
in Santa, plus she'll be extra
well-behaved for the whole year
so she doesn't blow it again.
Hold on, you kids want me
to trick Sabrina into being bad
just so she won't stop believing Santa?
Never in a million years would
I resort to something so low.
No, we better keep brainstorming
because I am definitely
not doing that idea.
How desperate do you think I am?
You are really scraping the
bottom of the barrel with that one.
No, I will clearly not be
pursuing that line of action.
No way, no how.
So, you want me to sit here
and watch the cookies
but not eat them?
This seems like a trick.
He's doing the thing
he said he wasn't gonna do!
These cookies are for Santa.
If anyone eats them, he'll be really mad.
I need you to guard them.
It's a very important job.
Well, I guess it is about time
I start earning my keep around here.
I knew I could count on you.
Remember, no matter what,
don't eat these delicious,
home made, fresh out of the oven,
warm, gooey, chocolate chip delights.
I'll leave you here alone...
with these cookies...
which are delicious.
Okay, cookies, it's just you and me.
Ooh, they look so yummy.
What would Mommy and Daddy say?
"Sabrina, I'm your Daddy and I say,
'Don't eat the cookies!'"
"Listen to your Father, honey,
he knows what's best."
Okay, Mommy and Daddy, I love you.
I don't think she's taking the bait.
That's because you didn't
put any milk out.
You can't have cookies without milk.
- That's like Wang without the Chung.
- Any chance she'll crack?
I'd say your odds are about as good
as a democrat being elected president.
Yeesh, I've heard of "lookie, lookie,
don't eat the cookie,"
but this is ridiculous.
What?
You guys got any other bright ideas?
Maybe I should go eat the cookies?
Well, if she's not gonna, somebody should.
- Oh, my God, it's Christmas!
- Oh, it's Christmas!
Yes, sensible winter socks!
You knew!
- Ooh, what could this be?
- Well, I wanted to make sure
you look really cool
on the back of that motorcycle.
You didn't! You didn't!
You didn't.
Motorcycle crashes are one of the
leading causes of brain injury.
If Joey Saratoga doesn't care about this,
then Joey Saratoga
doesn't care about you.
Wow, this present shows you really care,
so in a way it's even cooler
than a new leather jacket.
Take it from me,
being safe is totally radical.
Is this my present?
It's a Pretty Pony Princess play set,
just like you asked for.
- Is that it?
- Well, it's pretty cool.
She comes with a tiara and everything.
Oh, okay.
And cue the waterworks in 30, 29, 28...
...four, three, two, and...
- Hey, what's this?
- A letter? Who could this be from?
Open it, Sabrina.
Oh, wow.
Wow!
- Wow!
- What does it say?
How should I know?
I can't read.
"Dear Sabrina,
this is a letter from your parents.
Even though we can't be
with you on Christmas,
we're in heaven looking down on you
and we want you to know
we love you very much.
You are a good girl
and we are very proud of you.
Love, Your Mommy and Daddy."
Isn't that great, Sabrina?
A letter from your Mom and Dad.
- No, that's not what I asked for.
- Sabrina...
I didn't want a stupid letter,
I wanted my Mommy and Daddy.
- I know you're upset, but...
- I hate this.
I hate Santa Claus and I hate trees
and I hate you
and I hate Christmas!
Was it something I said?
Why would it be
something Ethan said?
No, that's the joke,
it wasn't something Ethan said,
- that's why it's funny.
- Oh... Okay.
- Can I come in?
- Even if I say no,
it's not like anyone ever listens
to what I want.
Sabrina, I really screwed things up.
I got so excited trying
to make you excited,
I forgot the true meaning of Christmas.
Christmas isn't about getting
everything you want.
It's about being around the people
that care about you.
I did everything right.
Why wouldn't Santa Claus
want me to be happy?
I'm sure he does, he just...
Santa Claus works in mysterious ways.
It's like when I make you eat vegetables.
Sure, they taste yucky,
but you have to trust that I know
what's good for you.
So, Santa Claus made
my parents dead because
- he thinks it's good for me?
- Yeah... No!
- Santa Claus didn't make your parents dead.
- But he didn't save them either.
No, he...
That's not how Santa works.
You said Santa Claus is always watching,
so if he's watching
why doesn't he help us?
Does he enjoy watching us be sad?
Is that how he gets his kicks?
- No!
- Are we all just pawns in Santa's sick game?
What kind of pervert is he?
Oh, no, Santa's watching us right now!
I'm sorry, Santa!
I didn't mean it.
Please don't hurt the people I love.
No, Sabrina, Santa Claus isn't real.
What?
He's a lie that grownups
made up because we like
to believe that there's
an order to the universe
and that good behavior
will lead to happiness,
but the fact is that just isn't true.
What?
You can't be good
just because you think
some fat guy in a red suit
is gonna bring you presents.
You have to be good just to be good.
That's all there is.
- Whoa...
- Look, I don't know why things happen,
I don't know why
some people get everything
and some people are orphans.
All I know is I spent last Christmas
alone at my office.
I didn't get a tree,
I didn't put up any decorations
or sing carols,
and I didn't try to get any little girls
to believe in Santa Claus.
Sabrina, you and Olivia and Ethan
are the best things that
have ever happened to me,
and if it took your parents
dying for you to be part
of my life, well, then
I'm glad your parents died.
Oh, you don't mean that.
No, I do, I'm glad
your parents are dead
and are never coming back.
Well, when you put it that way,
I guess I am, too.
I know that sometimes
I make a mess of this whole thing,
a horse raising three
human kids while also
juggling work and trying
to have a love life thing,
- but there's one more present.
- Is it from Santa Claus?
- No, it's from me.
- Oh!
Wow, pencils!
What do they say?
- Sound it out.
- Sa... Sab...
Sabrin...
rine...
Sab...
Sabrine...
Sabrinay.
- It says Sabrina.
- Oh!
I can't bring your Mommy and Daddy back,
but as long as I'm around,
you'll always have a place
to keep your pencils.
Thanks.
Maybe it's just because
I never had a Christmas before,
but this is the best
Christmas I've ever had.
Me, too.
Olivia, Ethan, look what I got!
Hello?
Listen, Mr. Liberatore,
I've given it a lot of thought
and I'm not...
Well, I'm not comin' in to work today.
If I have to choose between my career
and the people I care about,
well, then I'm sorry,
but I'm putting people first.
You know, it took guts
to call in and tell me that,
the kind of guts we need
on our executive board.
If that Scrooge, Jacob Goldstein,
wants to work on Christmas,
- he can work somewhere else!
- Fire that Jew!
I'm making you partner.
Well, I'm really glad
to hear that, Mr. Liberatore.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to go spend Christmas
with the people I love.
Hi, I'm a Pretty Pony Princess.
I'm a pencil.
Well, I guess everything turned out okay.
How'd you get her to come back down?
Let's just say I made her
an offer she couldn't refuse.
Yowza-yowza-bo-bowza!
Well, I gotta hand it to you,
even though it didn't work,
that letter you wrote
was really something.
I didn't write that letter.
I thought you wrote that letter.
- I didn't write the letter.
- Wasn't me.
Then where'd it come from?
Ho, ho, ho!
Well, that sucked.
So the letter was actually
from her parents?
Uh, I think it was from Santa.
That's why there was a
"ho, ho, ho" voice at the end.
So in the world of this show,
there is a Santa.
No, I don't know,
we were all on cocaine.
God, I can't believe I spent
nine years of my life
- making that dumb show.
- It wasn't all dumb, BoJack.
The episode where Sabrina
had a black friend
really started the conversation
about racism.
And the episode where
Ethan looked directly at
a solar eclipse really
started the conversation
about not looking directly
at a solar eclipse.
- Yeah...
- Well, anyway, Merry Christmas.
I know, it's really just another day
in a year full of days,
nothing all that special about it
other than the significance we give it,
but still, I'm glad I got to spend
part of the day with you, BoJack.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hey, um, Horsin' Around had
eight other Christmas episodes.
If you're not doing anything else today,
we could watch another one,
I mean, just to see how stupid it is.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
But don't talk in the middle of it.
- Zip!
- You can talk a little bit.
- Don't be weird about it.
- Okay.
Hey, after we watch "Horsin' Around,"
- can we make holiday cookies?
- No.
- Can we sing carols?
- Can we roast a Christmas goose?
- No.
- Can we play dreidel?
- Can we get a tree?
- No.
- Doesn't have to be a Christmas tree.
- Still no.
- Can we be visited by three spirits?
- No.
- Can we be visited by three kings?
Can we go outside
and make snow angels?
What snow?
It's 72 degrees out.
- Can we make driveway gravel angels?
- No.
- Can we drink eggnog?
- Bourbon and eggnog?
- No.
- What about just bourbon?
- Fine.
♪ It's Christmas time again ♪
♪ And that means Santa's in his sled ♪
♪ He's flyin' through the night time ♪
♪ Got presents in the morning ♪
♪ It's Christmas time again ♪
♪ And that means sleighin'
with your friends ♪
♪ Eatin' cookies by the fire ♪
♪ You can't sleep
'cause you're not tired ♪
♪ It's Christmas time
and all your friends are here ♪
let's ring in the New Year ♪
♪ Let's light the tree
and talk about the past ♪
♪ Do you believe in ♪
♪ I believe in you, Santa ♪
It's a Kazzaz-trophe!
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~