Good morning, morning.
Good morning, sun. Good morning, trees.
Good morning, busy buzzy bees.
Good morning, Sarah Lynn. Good
to see you, Sarah Lynn.
The tulips and
chrysanthemums are really coming in.
Good morning, handsome garden ants.
I like the way you plant my plants.
Your flowers make my feelings
dance. I like your
handsome planter pants.
Goddamn it! Why won't you...?
It's okay.
Sarah Lynn, you are calm, you are thin.
Your skin is so soft, it's like
you murdered a baby and stole its skin.
Your skin is "murdered-baby" soft.
Okay.
Blueberry, goji berry, flax,
chia, shark fin,
and... white rhino horn.
Sober, so good.
Oh.
- BoJack?
- Hey, Sarah Lynn.
- You wanna party?
- Oh, thank God. Yes!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Okay, hand me the açai.
- Is that how you pronounce it?
- Who knows?
They should really just
call them "overpriced
blueberries for douchebags."
- Ow.
- How's life?
Well, the truth is that...
Didn't catch that,
but everything's cool?
No. In fact, I've never felt so alone...
Sorry, missed it! You should
learn to talk louder, dude!
Oh, hey, bummer about
you getting the nomination,
but then, it turning out that
you didn't get the nomination.
It was big news yesterday.
Yeah, I got royally screwed,
know who was there for me?
No one, because everyone's an
asshole and the whole world sucks balls.
- Anyway, thanks for having me over.
- I'm with you, man.
Everything sucks! Especially sobriety.
Why would I make my body a temple?
I've been to Temple. Temple
is super boring.
What do you say we go on an epic bender?
Yes! Let's get higher than
a stilt walker's dick!
That's what I'm talking about.
Let's get some booze and drugs.
We can clear out my bank
account. I got nothing left I care about.
What do you mean "get"? This
whole house is booze and drugs.
- Here. -
Yogurt-covered raisins?
- Nope. Vicodin-covered
Vicodin. - Oh!
- LSD.
- Wow.
- Yah! Crystal
meth. - Ha-ha!
Ee-yah!
Cocaine... No! That's drywall.
Ugh! Where the hell did
I hide the cocaine?
Oh, yeah, I also told the
liquor store to deliver.
To nine months of sobriety.
To life and being done with it!
Okay, okay. What about this one?
Remember when Erika Eleniak
guest starred as Goober's
cousin from out of town,
and Brad had a boner
for the whole episode?
- What? No.
- You can totally see it in every scene.
Cold open, boner! Act one, boner!
Commercial break... "Hello, we're from
the Wheaties corporation!"
Back to boners!
Okay, we'll put it on the
list. We gotta watch that one.
What about the one where the
writers made Joelle dress
up like a pumpkin,
and the whole episode
was fat jokes,
so then Joelle got
an eating disorder?
Everything was so
much simpler back then.
She had to go to a clinic. She
missed, like, five episodes.
We didn't know how good we had it.
We got to come to work
and have fun every day,
and we weren't worried about
our legacy or awards.
Because buildings are
supposed to be rectangles, goddamn it!
Wait, what were we talking about?
We were talking about Horsin' Around.
Then, you had to go pee.
Then, you came back covered
in toilet paper
and pretended to be a mummy.
Then, you took it all off because
you decided Egypt was stupid,
especially pyramids,
because you think
triangle buildings
are, and I quote,
"gauche as shit."
That does sound like me, but
I don't remember any of that.
I must have blacked out. Maybe I
should lay off the alcohol for...
and I said, "You're sitting
on the pizza, Mr. President."
- Whoa! I think I just had another one.
- Another what? Pizza?
No, blackout. The thing we
were just talking about.
- Try to keep up here.
- Oh...
Boom! Boner! Pay
up! What did I tell you?
That's not a boner. It's a shadow.
Well, I think we all learned
a valuable lesson today
about the Armenian genocide.
The Armenian genocide was too much, man!
All right! Next episode.
Why can't life be like
it was on Horsin' Around?
All our issues conveniently
settled in 22 hilarious minutes.
You know, it's amazing that
it's legal for kids to be actors.
How is that not child labor? I
didn't know what I was signing up for.
- I was three.
- This is getting me depressed.
Let's do something fun.
Oh! Okay, you know
what really kicks ass?
The planetarium!
You get crazy high in the parking lot,
then you go in and get your mind
blown by all the trippy
galaxies and shit.
That sounds stupid. I'm
gonna be in charge of the fun.
No, no, no! That was drywall.
Jesus, we have to start marking
our drugs more clearly.
Let's just take a box of whiskey and go.
Whoo!
- It was just so hard.
- Wha...? What the...?
I was stuck in a terrifying
cycle of drinking, lifting my head up,
drinking, lifting my head
up, drinking, lifting my head up.
Coffee, stale donuts,
attention hogs telling
boring stories about themselves?
- Jesus! Are we at a 12-step
meeting? - Now, you're a detective?
Last night, you couldn't even
solve the mystery of
where the toilet is.
So, all our partying
was an elaborate trick
just to get me to go sober?
No, Detective Pukes in
the Washing Machine.
You're here because I couldn't
leave you alone in my house,
and I had to come today.
Gotta get my nine-month chip.
Chip? We've been wasted for... 31 hours?
That's no reason for
me to not get my chip.
That's literally exactly the
reason you shouldn't get your chip.
Nowhere in the 12 steps
does it say to not drink.
That's not actually one
of the steps. Loophole.
Take a swig.
If you have to listen to losers
talk about their shitty sober lives,
it's a lot more fun to be buzzed.
And I realized people don't
change because they want to change.
They change because they have to change.
Oh, God. Boo!
Oh, booing is
generally frowned upon here.
How else am I supposed to
express how boring these stories are?
My name is
Simon and I'm an alcoholic.
Hi, Simon.
My rock bottom was when I
actually woke up under a rock.
Can't get lower than that.
Come on! You people
call yourself drunks?
Most of this is stuff I do on
a daily basis completely sober.
Trust me, pal, we've
done some awful things.
One time, I didn't
want my friend to move out,
so I used character actress Ann
Dowd to help me sabotage
his hip-hopera.
Oh, please, that's baby stuff.
You so-called drunks want something
to feel shitty about?
- BoJack, maybe we should go.
- I got somethin' for ya. Whoa.
My name is BoJack.
Hi, BoJack.
Oh, like you didn't know?
Anyway, I once went all the way down to
New Mexico to see a
woman that I knew,
and she had a young daughter, Penny.
Penny Carson. That's her real
name. You can look her up.
I don't care.
And first, I tried to sleep with
the mom, but she said no.
Then, I tried to sleep with the daughter.
Then, the mom walked in on me trying
to sleep with the daughter,
and I was like, "Oopsie-doopsie!
Exit stage right!"
Oh, God.
The worst part is, I don't even
know what happened after I left.
Did I ruin the family? Did I
scar that little girl for life?
I don't know. I'll never know.
And that's just, like,
one of a billion things
that I have going through
my head all the time.
So, anyone got a better story than that?
Wow.
Didn't think so, bitches.
Where's my trophy, or chip, or whatever?
Whoa!
That was impressive, BoJack.
I've never seen them
cancel an AA meeting
because everyone got
bummed out before.
Uh, what are you talking about?
You told everyone
about that Penny chick.
Then, you went on and on about
how you're never going to change.
Then, you chased the slug around,
threatening to pour salt on his head.
I talked about Penny?
Hey! We've all done
shitty stuff before.
Most of us aren't as proud
of it as you seem to be.
I'm not proud. I feel really terrible
that I might have really messed that girl up.
Oh, she's fine. I looked
her up on Facebook.
She's going to Oberlin,
likes Thai food and
the smell of a
fire on the first really
cold day of winter.
That doesn't mean anything. Everyone
likes the smell of fire
on the first cold day of winter.
You know, I used to
feel just like you
before I got into this
"12 steps" thing.
They taught me how to make amends.
You just say you're
sorry for the things you did
and you get a clean slate.
So, what? Just dirty up the slate again.
Then, you just make amends again.
It's a never-ending cycle,
where you always end up feeling
good about yourself.
- No!
- You know what?
This may be the
nitrous and bath salts talking,
but I want to do some
more nitrous and bath salts.
And then, let's
make some goddamn amends.
Maybe you should start with the
family whose playhouse
you just smashed.
- Oh, no!
- Oh. Hey, kid!
I'm sorry your lame dad
built such a cheap-ass playhouse!
Yeah, you gotta use
parallel joints
to support that
foundation, dumbshit!
- Also, suck a dick!
- You know what? I do feel better.
- I don't think they're home.
- So, we wait.
I need to make amends to Diane,
and we're not leaving until I do.
But it's boring out
here, and I'm hungry and I'm bored!
I bet they have food inside.
Let's see if I still have
that spare key. Here it is.
Yes!
Okay, after we get food,
remind me that this is another
thing I need to make amends for.
Where are those two?
They did not keep their
fridge stocked enough
for two stoned people waiting
around for hours.
It's only been, like, ten
minutes. You have a real thing with food.
That's what happens when you
mix the appetite of a horse
with the appetite of
someone with a hole inside him
that needs to be constantly
filled with attention, food, and sex.
- Pass the Bugles.
- There's no more Bugles.
There's no more of
anything. Let's just go.
- I can't leave until I make amends.
-  I got a idea!
My name is BoJack's friend
What's-Her-Face and I wear glasses.
Do you have
something to say to me, BoJack?
- Am I BoJack or Mr. Peanutbutter?
- You can be anyone you want.
This is your dream... dream... dream...
Stop doing that. We're both
awake. Let's just get to this.
Diane, I'm sorry I
said mean things to you.
That's cool. I forgive you. Wait,
would my character say that?
What's Diane's deal again?
She's, like, an Asian Daria?
- She's a little more complex.
- But she's basically Asian Daria, right?
With the glasses and the
jacket and her whole "blah" thing.
Okay, shut up. Now,
I'll be Mr. Peanutbutter
and you make amends to me.
Who's Mr. Peanutbutter?
And, now, you be Mr.
Carolyn and I'll be Princess Diana.
Oh, yeah. Good idea.
Um... should we do something about this?
Hey, why don't you two sleep
this off in our guest room?
Oh, my God, that
mirror is talking to us!
You can't stop us, us from the future!
We're making amends, assholes!
Ow! Come on!
- That felt so good!
- See?
When you make amends, don't
you just feel lighter?
Well, I also ate a shit
ton of Bugles, so no.
But I do feel like we got to the
bottom of who really
killed Princess Di.
- It was all of us.
- Next stop, Todd!
Todd, I'm sorry. I want to take full
responsibility for what happened,
even though it is not my
fault and I did nothing wrong.
Emily is an adult woman who
can make her own choices.
And besides, are you
even really into girls?
- I mean, what is your deal?
- Uh...
- Hey, what are you doing with our son?
Wait, you're BoJack Horseman.
I am, and this is my
best buddy Todd.
That movie star has
really taken a shine to our boy.
You think this is our big break?
You don't think he's
inappropriately interested, do you?
What? No. But if he is, that
could also be a big break.
I'm just saying.
- Hey, wait!
- Hold on. Where are you going?
- Come back.
- You want to take Todd for a sleepover?
- Sleepover?
- No offense, Todd,
but your parents are creeping me out.
To the next amends!
- What do you want, BoJack?
- I don't know.
I'm very drunk and a little nauseous,
but if I'm here in your
house, it must be to make amends.
- Amends... for what?
- I don't know.
Whatever it is that you think
I did to make you disappear.
- BoJack...
- How could you leave me like that
when I needed you most?
I'm sorry, BoJack. I thought you
were a winner. I was wrong.
This is hard for me,
too. I staked my reputation...
No, this is not about
the Oscar campaign.
How could you think that this
is about the Oscar campaign?
We had something more, didn't we?
- You've been drinking.
- Well, not just drinking.
Yes, Ana, I'm a mess.
Whoa! I am a broken,
screwed-up misfit toy,
and you act all in control,
but I know that, deep
down, you're broken, too.
And I don't know why
you won't just give
us a chance to be
broken together.
What about that doesn't appeal to you?
BoJack, when I was in
college, I had a job as a lifeguard...
Wait, did we just go to Ana's
house? Did I get closure?
If by "closure" you mean I lit
her ottoman on fire, then yes.
We gotta go back.
- What the hell?
- I know I was just here,
but I feel like you told
me some important story
that explained everything about us.
Unfortunately, I totally spaced it.
Gotta be honest. I've
had a couple beers.
Ugh! All right, I'll tell you
again, if it'll make you leave.
When I was a lifeguard, I...
- Oh, crud.
- You want to go back to Ana's, don't you?
I feel like I'll
definitely get it this time.
Lifeguard...
- One more time?
- No. This time I wrote it down.
"I'm a lifeguard. This woman's
house smells weird, or is that me?
Pay attention, Sarah Lynn.
Don't do that thing where
you write down your thoughts
instead of what the
person is actually saying.
I wonder if it's time to
get my boobs done again."
- Mm-hmm.
-  That's very helpful.
Thank you. Who's next?
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Okay, so I know I keep
bothering you tonight.
Tonight? I haven't
seen you in two weeks.
Oh, really?
I just need to know what you were trying
to tell me about being a lifeguard,
and then, I'll leave and
you'll never see me again.
Mmm...
After I almost
drowned, I decided I
would never again be
weaker than water.
So, I became a lifeguard.
On my first day of
training, my instructor told me
that there are going to be times when
you'll see someone in trouble.
You're going to want to rush in
there and do whatever
you can to save them,
but you have to stop yourself,
because there are some
people you can't save.
'Cause those people will
thrash and struggle
and try to take you down with them.
What does that have to do with me?
What the...? Where the hell are we now?
- Ohi...
- Ojai?
- We drove all the way to Ojai?
- Let me finish.
Ohi, and here's the kicker... O.
- Ohio.
- We drove all the way to Ohio?!
I wanted to go to the
planetarium, but you
demanded we come here.
You said you had to make one
more amend, to that Penny girl.
What? No! That is a terrible idea.
Let's turn this car around right now.
Uh...
- I feel we didn't turn the car around.
- No, we did,
but then, you turned it back around
because you really
wanted to find that deer girl,
so we decided to do a stakeout.
There was a whole makeover
sequence, where we went to the mall
and tried on different
trench coats for each other.
Do you not remember any of that?
This is insane. I already
scarred her for life.
If I see her again, I'll just end up
getting my horribleness all over her.
You think it's too late
for me to go to college?
I always wanted to be an architect.
But one of those architects,
where, at night, she's
a high-end call girl,
and, by day, she's an
international superspy.
- So, when is she an architect?
- I don't know. Frontier times?
No, I didn't mean what era.
If she's a call girl at
night and a spy during the day...
- Hey, look, Penny.
- Oh, God, what's she doing?
- Does she look emotionally damaged?
- She's just going to the computer.
She's probably in a sex chat
room with some middle-aged horse
because that's the only
way she can still feel love.
- Yeah, probably.
- Or she's so upset about what you did
that she's using the Internet
to find ways to commit suicide.
That makes even more sense.
All right, we've
established that you ruined her.
- Can we go back to L.A. now?
- Yes.
So... obviously, I wanted to keep
following Penny because I'm an idiot.
Let's just nip this in the bud.
I'm gonna write "Do not
follow Penny" on my hands
in the unlikely scenario
of my blacking out again.
I'll just write "Follow
Penny" on this hand,
and then, on this hand, I'll write...
- Goddamn it!
- What?
We're just doing what the hand said.
- Uh, what?
- The hand demanded donuts.
- There she is.
- She's drinking beer.
Oh, God, this is just like the
episode of Horsin' Around
when Olivia went to the frat party,
but Penny doesn't have a kind
angel played by Jose Canseco
to help her get out of this jam!
Ugh. Okay, now, I'm bored
again. Quit hoggin' the 'nocs.
She's just drinking Red
Bull. Wait. Now, she's leaving.
Hey, look, it's the Obertones!
Love your sound, dudes!
- ♪ Thank you ♪
- ♪ Thank you! ♪
She seems... fine.
Too fine, like she's hiding a dark
secret that's eating away at her soul.
Or, possibly... she's fine.
Maybe I didn't ruin her life.
Hey, you were a father figure, who
was sexually inappropriate to me,
and I turned out perfect.
- Now, can we please go home?
- Okay, good plan.
I'll just go pee out the last 20 beers.
Whoa. Look at
me, walking good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
No, no, no! Shush, shush.
- BoJack?
- Oh!
- What are you doing here?
- Hey, Penny!
- Did you come here to find me?
- No, I...
You can't be here. I-I
don't want to see you here.
I don't want to see you at all. I
was 17. I didn't know any better.
- I tried...
- You need to leave.
It's BoJack Horseman and Sarah Lynn!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
BoJack, we need to
get out of here now.
Can I get a selfie
and another selfie
if the first selfie
doesn't look good?
BoJack, over here!
Penny, no.
Penny?
You know, on the plus
side, she really seemed okay.
Mm-hmm.
Until she saw you and freaked out.
But she probably would have been totally
fine if you'd never shown up.
- Oh, God.
- I think the wound was completely healed
before you reopened it by showing
up unannounced at her college
and all the pain
came rushing back to her.
Oh, good Lord!
In a way, it's like you
destroyed her life twice.
- Will you please stop talking about it?
- Okay, fine.
Whoop.
Man, Ohio sucks!
Next time, could you almost
molest someone who
lives in Hawaii?
You could be bummed
out at a luau right now.
Let's just go home.
- You got a bottle opener?
- Glove compartment.
Well, I'll be a dick sucked by
a dumbshit! What do we have here?
Oh, that? Turns out there's a
brand of heroin called BoJack.
Dude, that's a big freaking deal.
Getting a drug named after you
is cooler than getting an Oscar.
I mean, there's Billy Crystal
Meth, Angel Dustin Hoffman,
Lucille Eightball and now you.
It's a rarefied breed,
man. Congratulations!
- Thank you?
- Oh, we have to do BoJack!
- It's too perfect.
- I don't know.
There's that old saying. "Liquor
before beer, never fear.
Don't do heroin."
"I'm BoJack. Please, put me inside you."
I'm not gonna shoot
heroin with you, Sarah Lynn.
We can snort heroin like
sophisticated adults.
Way ahead of you.
Okay, thank you. Happy
Thanksgiving 2007.
Why did you just say what year it is?
I guess I just get nervous talking
to network executives.
This last episode got
the worst ratings yet.
I was afraid your character trying
heroin would be a bridge too far.
- Oh.
- And the disjointed blackout structure,
with the one flashback in the middle,
really confused our audience.
Yeah.
They hated all the
fourth-wall-breaking meta jokes.
Of course. Audiences hate meta
jokes. When will comedy writers learn?
BoJack, I know there is an
audience out there for our show.
We just need to find a way to
get more people to check us out.
I know what you're
thinking... Full frontal.
I was thinking guest star.
We need a celebrity who is
incredibly popular right now, like...
- Oh, what about Sarah Lynn?
- Ooh, that's genius!
Sarah Lynn? I don't know. I
haven't spoken to her in years.
Besides, she's not
gonna want to do this.
She's the world's biggest pop star.
She's the only hope we
have to keep this show alive.
Would you ask her? I'm
sure she'd do it for you.
You're like a father to her.
- So, what is it?
- What is what?
You were mumbling about how
you had to ask me something.
Oh! Um, never mind. Hey, how
long have we known each other?
- Feels like our entire lives.
- Well, my entire life, pretty much.
We were on a TV show. Isn't that insane?
Yeah, it's pretty wild.
You know, sometimes it feels like you're
the only one who really understands me,
because how could anyone else?
Nobody knows what we went
through, nobody who
wasn't on that show.
But we knew each other
before we were anybody,
and that's how we can
be friends, because
we're not like those
other people.
The people who glom onto you because
of who they think you are,
and they think they can sleep on
your couch and eat your food.
They think you're
gonna save their agency.
I never asked for that kind of pressure,
but you and me, we don't
want anything from each other.
You know, I... I could
never figure out what love meant,
but, right now, I don't
need to figure out anything.
I just feel it. I love you, Sarah Lynn.
Sarah Lynn?
- Sarah Lynn?
- What?
- Oh, my God! Thank God you're okay!
- I'm not okay. I'm bored.
This hotel room is boring!
What's on TV?
- The Oscars are on.
- Really?
- How long have we been on this bender?
- I love the Oscars.
The red carpet, the fashion,
all the magic of Hollywoo wrapped
up in one exciting night.
And the winner for
Best Original Song is...
"The Silly Banana Song (Love Theme)"
from The Nazi Who Played
Yahtzee by Sarah Lynn.
Get your ass up here, girl.
I won! Oh, my God!
I forgot I was even nominated.
I accept this on her behalf.
And if you're watching this, Sarah Lynn,
wherever you are, please come home.
Oh, man, I should have been there.
When I was a kid, if you'd
told me I'd win an Oscar,
I'd never have believed it.
And, now, I've done it and...
BoJack... I don't...
like anything about me.
- Hey.
- None of this is me.
These boobs aren't me.
- This house isn't me.
- We're not at your house right now.
The only reason I wear this shirt
is because some company paid
me $8,000 to wear it.
And I don't even need the money.
I just liked that someone
still wanted me to wear their shirt.
Hey, hey, hey, it's okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
What am I supposed to
do? I don't know what to do.
Am I doomed? Are you
doomed? Are we all doomed?
No, no! Calm down. Nobody is doomed.
And I'll tell you what we're gonna do.
We're gonna go to the planetarium.
Really?
Our solar system formed about
four and a half billion years ago...
- Isn't this place amazing?
- Totally.
I always forget that there
are more than just the six stars
you can see in the Los Angeles sky.
Yeah, that's cool, too, but
I meant this building.
It's a giant dome. Domes are so cool.
I prefer rectangular
buildings, as I firmly established.
I wanna be an architect.
...be it horse,
cat, human, or even lizard,
our lives are but the briefest flashes
in a universe that is
billions of years old.
See, Sarah Lynn, we're not doomed.
In the great grand scheme of
things, we're just tiny specks
that will one day be forgotten.
So, it doesn't matter what we did in
the past, or how
we'll be remembered.
The only thing that
matters is right now, this moment,
this one spectacular
moment we are sharing together.
Right, Sarah Lynn?
Sarah Lynn?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --